npidb.org 2012-06-17

# NPIdb - National Provider Identifier DataBase Privacy Policy

 NPI Number Lookup for Doctors

NPIdb.org - Our Privacy Policy

NPIdb.org respect your right to privacy. None of the information we collect is passed on to other parties, except when required as part of the business services we provide for you, or as required under United States law. 

**Data Collection**   
We collect no data about you except for that captured by a cookie to provide us with anonymous information about site navigation. 

**Cookies**   
Cookies are small pieces of text information created by websites and stored on your computer. We only use cookies to provide us with anonymous information about site navigation. No other information is stored in cookies, and cookies are not used for any other purpose. You should also be aware that whilst the above paragraph describes our use of cookies, some advertisers on this site may also collect data using cookies. The use of cookies and/or web beacons to collect data is used in the ad serving process. We do not have access to this data. Google uses the DART cookie to serve ads to our users based on their previous visits to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

**Protection**   
We will not retain any details that you provide, except for your email address if you contact us and this will never be disclosed to third parties. Customers are free to opt out of the news services by following the instructions on the bottom of each news email if subscribed to. 

**Links**   
This website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage you, when you leave this website, to read the privacy statements/policies of each and every website you visit, as this particular privacy policy applies solely to this particular website. 
  *[NPI]: National Provider Identifier
